Yehezkiel W

Summary

A Fullstack Software Engineer with Focus on Backend with 3+ years of experience as developer, intern and volunteer • A Cyber Security, DevOps and Machine Learning Enthusiast with experience as Penetration Tester at DPTSI ITS, DevSecOps at Volvinco and Machine Learning Thesis • A Computer Science / Informatics Engineering freshgraduate in Institut Teknologi Sepuluh Nopember (ITS), Surabaya.

To learn more, visit yehezkiel-wiradhika.vercel.app

✓.

Quick Guide

- Each section title is arbitrary and each section contains a list of entries.
- \circ There are 7 unique entry types: BulletEntry, TextEntry, EducationEntry, ExperienceEntry, NormalEntry, PublicationEntry, and OneLineEntry.
- Select a section title, pick an entry type, and start writing your section!
- Here **Z**, you can find a comprehensive user guide for RenderCV.

Education

University of Pennsylvania

Sept 2000 - May 2005

BS in Computer Science

- \circ GPA: 3.9/4.0 (a link to somewhere \square)
- o Coursework: Computer Architecture, Comparison of Learning Algorithms, Computational Theory

Experience

Software Engineer

Cupertino, CA

Apple

June 2005 - Aug 2007

- Reduced time to render user buddy lists by 75% by implementing a prediction algorithm
- Integrated iChat with Spotlight Search by creating a tool to extract metadata from saved chat transcripts and provide metadata to a system-wide search database
- Redesigned chat file format and implemented backward compatibility for search

Software Engineer Intern

Redmond, WA

Microsoft

June 2003 - Aug 2003

- Designed a UI for the VS open file switcher (Ctrl-Tab) and extended it to tool windows
- o Created a service to provide gradient across VS and VS add-ins, optimizing its performance via caching
- Built an app to compute the similarity of all methods in a codebase, reducing the time from $\mathcal{O}(n^2)$ to $\mathcal{O}(n\log n)$
- Created a test case generation tool that creates random XML docs from XML Schema
- Automated the extraction and processing of large datasets from legacy systems using SQL and Perl scripts

Publications

3D Finite Element Analysis of No-Insulation Coils

Jan 2004

Frodo Baggins, Yehezkiel Wiradhika, Samwise Gamgee

10.1109/TASC.2023.3340648

Projects

Multi-User Drawing Tool

- Developed an electronic classroom where multiple users can simultaneously view and draw on a "chalkboard" with each person's edits synchronized
- ∘ Tools Used: C++, MFC

Synchronized Desktop Calendar

- Developed a desktop calendar with globally shared and synchronized calendars, allowing users to schedule meetings with other users
- ∘ Tools Used: C#, .NET, SQL, XML

Custom Operating System

2002

- o Built a UNIX-style OS with a scheduler, file system, text editor, and calculator
- o Tools Used: C

Technologies

Languages: C++, C, Java, Objective-C, C#, SQL, JavaScript

Technologies: .NET, Microsoft SQL Server, XCode, Interface Builder